hikarabita kotoba wo tsunai de
connecting old words that have been used up
soredemo bokura shinpuru na omoi wo tsutaetai dake na no
I just want to convey my simple thoughts
fukinukeru kusunda ano hi no kaze wa
that day's faint wind blows away
kinou no haikyo ni uchi sutete
at the castle ruins of yesterday
kimi to warau ima wo ikiru no da
I'll laugh with you and live for the moment
soredemo ano dekigoto ga kimi wo kurushimeru daro
still that incident will continue to trouble you, right?
dakarakoso sayonara nanda
that's why it must be good-bye
konomama nanimo nokorazu ni anata to wakachiau dake
leaving nothing behind, let us share what is left
yagate bokura wa sore ga subetee dato kigatsuite
in time, we'll realize that it was everything
kanashimi wa hoo wo tsutatte namida no kawa ni naru dake
and sadness will touch our cheeks, creating a river of tears
yureru omoi wa tsuyoi uzu ni natte tokeau no yo
Trembling thoughts swept into a vortex and melting away
I'm counting on you, Choji!
Yeah!
Expansion Jutsu!
All right, let's go!
Human Boulder!
What?!
Choji... You are awesome after all!
Full Power!
Burn, Choji
They got away from
my Barrier Ninjutsu...
He's the only one here.
Seems like the others went ahead.
Yeah.
They're not around
here any more.
Damn... Just when we thought
we caught up.
Everybody you did well...
for some losers.
What?!
Who are you calling losers?!
Once we're out it's our battle to win!
I-I will do it!
Wait, you two!
It's dangerous to fight them
head on right now!
We tore through the barrier!
We can do this!
Tunneling Fang!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
— Take this!
You guys are my meal!
Damn it!
Shoulder Charge!
Knee Lift!
Not even good enough for an appetizer!
Be careful everyone!
Another tricky one is coming!
Earth Style Barrier:
Earth Dome Prison!
Expansion Jutsu!
Human Boulder!
Damn!
Such useless acts...
There's no time.
We're going to split into two here!
Why?!
I see...
Even at 5 against 1
with our Chakras taken away
he's not someone we can
easily defeat...
If we take our time,
Sasuke will pass the borders.
If that happens we won't be able
to handle this on our own.
So we split up...
one team to stop him
and one to go after Sasuke, right?
Yeah. The sub leader is going
to be you Neji.
I found them!
Neji! Take Kiba and Choji
and go after Sasuke!
Got it!
This guy...
Naruto and I will handle it!
Are you going to put
the Shadow Paralysis Jutsu on me again?
Such a foolish Jutsu.
I don't need to see that kind of
street performance more than once!
And who was it that got tricked
by that street performance earlier?
He disappeared?!
Behind us!
Earth Style: Sphere of Graves!
He's nuts!
Be careful!
There's another one coming!
You are the platoon leader
if I'm not mistaken.
You sure do suffer
when you have a stupid leader.
You underlings!
A stupid leader like this...
I'll get rid of for you!
Expansion Jutsu! Human Boulder!
Thanks! Choji...
Why? Wasting my good intentions...
If the leader is stupid
then I guess the subordinates are losers.
Well... I'll kill you losers
before you suffer
working under
a glum shadow lover like him!
Damn, damn! Babbling on like that!
I will...!
He's mine!
I will... take care of him!
Choji...
What are you saying?!
He's not the kind of guy
you can handle on your own!
I will do it!
Choji... you...
Shikamaru...
Take these Food Pills for everyone...
Choji... You are not...
That's right.
I have that secret weapon of mine.
But Choji that is...!
Huh... Losers, I won't let you
have your way!
He's coming!
I'll get rid of you all here!
Go everyone!
Pills of three colors?
They're not Food Pills.
What are they?
First... Spinach Pill!
Get out of the way! Loser!
Impossible... He stopped me?!
Shikamaru, take everybody and go!
Choji...
What did we gather for?
If we lose Sasuke
then we will end up like he said...
The stupid leader and his losers!
You better catch up with us, Choji!
Yeah.
Everybody go!
All right! Let's go everyone!
— Yeah!
— Right!
Choji...
I'm going to get rid of you quick
and get rid of those guys too!
It won't be that easy...
What?!
I will...
...stop you!
A parting gift from Choji...
Eat it!
Yeah!
Thanks Choji...
Kiba!
Thanks!
Shikamaru...
That pill that Choji took earlier..
It seemed like some sort
of trump card
but does he have a chance to win?
He said that he has a secret weapon.
He brought the Akimichi clan's
ultimate secret pills on this mission...
These are the Triad colored Pills
of green, yellow, and red.
If you take it
you can gain explosive powers.
The energy that each pill
contains is enormous!
I see! I see!
So that's why he was so confident!
But... there's always a side effect
to any pills that work too well.
Damn... I didn't think it would hurt
so much with just the Spinach Pill.
I hope that Choji can settle it
with just the green pill.
Don't take the red one
no matter what, Choji.
I'm going to finish you at once!
Expansion Jutsu!
Spiky Human Boulder.
He raised the rotational
and destructive power
by using the Kunai Knives as spikes!
Earth Style: Terra Shield.
What?!
I-I did it...?
Yeah. That's what I was thinking too.
Akamaru...
What is he saying?
You know that Akamaru
can tell the strength of the enemy
just by the smell, right?
He's worried if Choji is going to be able
to handle that monster with just the pills.
True...
If we were to assess
the situation objectively
that giant's ability is unknown...
The possibility of Choji being able
to defeat him might be close to zero.
But...
That is how battle is...
Don't get carried away, loser!
Shatter Palm!
Did you know?
When there's a group of people
of five or so
there's always one loser.
That person is always made fun of...
and when it comes down to it
they'll just toss that person
aside like a pawn.
I'm talking about you!
Choji. All you want to do is eat.
You should train some at least!
You get teased because you're like that.
You're just a f...
You said somebody exceptional, right?
Shouldn't we ask Shino or somebody?!
This guy is useless too...
That is true...
No matter how hard I try on my own...
I...
Seems like I hit it right on the nose.
Seems like the Leaf is lacking in people
seeing that they pick a loser
like you to be on the pursuit team.
Why don't we finish this up already?!
Knee Lift!
Shoulder Charge!
Huh! You really are a loser to the end!
Your high spirit didn't last long at all
only at the beginning...!
You really are the ideal loser!
A loser like you shouldn't have come
to a place like this!
You should blame your stupid leader
for choosing you!
Shikamaru...
Neji's right. It's how a battle is.
From the start this mission
wasn't for recreation.
It's life or death.
Hey, Shikamaru...
I already anticipated the worst scenario
in which we would be fighting
separately on our own.
And at this point
if we're not prepared for
"one person, one kill"
we might not be able
to catch up to Sasuke.
Choji is a good guy
but he doesn't have the confidence.
He thinks that
he's the weakest of all of us.
He actually is weak.
Anybody can see that.
That's why he was the first to
stay behind to try to be useful.
Just as I thought...
But...
Choji and I have worked as a team
for many years
so coordinating with him
is easiest for me.
But Shikamaru...
But if we fight against each other
you might be stronger.
I might have given up fighting
against you too.
And you're you...
But...
Shikamaru... has always...
Shikamaru has always
believed in me...
Choji... are you ready?!
He believed that I was really strong!
That's why he left it up to me alone!
Just as I thought...
So everybody thinks that...
But... I know...
More than myself or Neji
or any of us here...
He is stronger!
And... I believe it.
Oh? Pretty impressive Chakra.
But... it's a far cry
from being a main dish...
Let's go, fatso!
Don't you say that!
Partial Expansion Jutsu!
GET UP aa sumimasen
get up! oh, I'm sorry
goku tama ni boku tama ni
once in a long while, once in a while
yume ni yabureru hito no kakera ga
the remnants of a person broken by dreams
yama no you ni mieru
kamisama ni hotokesama ni
clinging to God, clinging to Buddha
sugari naiteru hito no kakera ga
the remnants of a person crying
yama no you ni mieru
danran dansu de RANDEBUU
rendezvous with a happy dance circle
ore shouri no poozu da randaran
this is my victory pose, round and around
SHEIKU SHEIKU SHEIKU sagasou janai
shake shake shake let's look
owaranai baibai no RIZUMU de
with a bye-bye rhythm that never ends
yama no you ni mieru
I can't move because of the pain.
I didn't think the side effects
of the secret pill would be strong.
What do I do?
I only have one more pill.
But if I take it if I take it
I will... surely...
Next time:
"Goodbye, My Friend...! Even So, I Believe."
Of all people
I cannot forgive you!